Jack Levreau Full-Stack Developer

An aspiring Full-Stack Developer with a passion for open source development and three years of training experience, I've been leading groups and participating in hackathons for over five years while teaching and sharing my love of web development with others.

6354 N Sheridan Rd Clovis, CA 93619, USA +1 559 470-7049 Jack.levreau@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/jacklevreau

EXPERIENCE

Kyrion Studios, Freelance

Game Developer

Aug 2022 - Present • 2 mos

 Developing the essential core mechanics for each independent game developed by Kyrncion Studios

Kyrncion Studios, Freelance

Web Developer

May 2022 - Aug 2022 · 4 mos

- Full-Stack Developer at Kyrncion Studios, working on our company's website
- Managing and maintaining our company's servers, which are used to host and distribute our games

SKILLS

JavaScript Kotlin MongoDB MySQL PHP

Node.js

Linux Git

EDUCATION

Clovis High School

High-School Diploma Aug 2022 - Jun 2023 Clovis, CA

- Clubs: Founder of Clovis
 High's first Computer
 Science-based activity
 club, the Web
 Development Club
- Activities: Academic
 Decathlon member for
 Clovis High specializing
 in mathematics

The Center for Advanced Research and Technology

Aug 2021 - Jun 2023

Clovis, CA

Classes: Web
 Application
 Development ROP &
 Interactive Game
 Design ROP

OTHER

- Courses: JavaScript and React courses offered by BitWise Industries
- Certificates: Design and Process & Cloud Data Engineer Professional Certificate